Guide to the Bernard and Jewel Bellush Papers WAG.030
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Unprocessed Files, 1940s-2000., 31770
  - NYC Politics and Immigrants (Clippings), 1990; 32127 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - University of Vermont, Lecture at, Apr 1999; 32126 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Benjamin Duarte: Painter-Carpenter-Roofing, 1997; 32125 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Petaluma Jewish Community, 2000-2001; 32124 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - PSC/CUNY Federal Credit Union, 1998; 32123 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - NGO Committee on Disarmament: Publication Committee, Feb 2001; 32122 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - NGO Committee on Disarmament: Publication Committee, Mar 2001; 32121 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - NGO Committee on Disarmament: Publication Committee, Apr 2001; 32120 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - NGO Committee on Disarmament: Publication Committee, May 2001; 32119 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Randolph A. Phillip, 1979-2001; 32118 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Rhone River, Paris, 2001; 32117 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - All Weather Guard Roofing, 1998; 32116 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Ross, Norman and family, 1999; 32115 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Scopes Trial: 70 Years Later, 2001; 32114 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Scopes Trial: 70 Years Later (Clippings), 1996; 32113 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Social Security, 1999; 32112 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Dr. Steven Spencer, 2000; 32111 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Stoler, Mark, 1998-2000; 32110 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Tax Speech II, 1998; 32109 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Norman Thomas High School, 1999; 32108 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Tyler, Gus, 1991-2001; 32107 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Triangle Fire, 1997; 32106 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Jewish Cemetery (Venice, Italy), 2000; 32105 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Candlelight Vigil: Assassinations of Shepard, Matthew and D. Barnett Slepian, 1998; 32104 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Freedman, James (Winant), 1996-1997; 32103 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Women in War by Willenz, June, Undated; 32102 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Workmen's Circle: Social and Economic Justice Committee, 2001; 32101 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - World Veterans Federation, 1998; 32100 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence, Oct 2007-Jan 2001; 32099 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Aug 2000-Oct 2000; 32098 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Heritage), 1933-1954; 32097 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - TVA The New Deal, 1935-1945; 32096 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Transcendentalists, Undated; 32095 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Carter Administration, 1977-1981; 32094 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - American Labor Party and Henry Wallace, 1970; 32093 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson, 1973-1981; 32092 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Browder, Earl, 1935-1979; 32091 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - CUNY: Radical Movements, 1929-1935, 1965-1984; 32090 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Old Left: War Our Heritage, 1936; 32089 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Baldwin, Bettie, 1935; 32088 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. as Governor, 1982; 32087 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - "What's Left? And Where Do We Go From Here?, 1971; 32086 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Old/New Left Views of the Roosevelt Presidency, 1976; 32085 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - LaGuardia, Fiorello (Mayor), 1966; 32084 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Tonkin Gulf Crisis, 1964; 32083 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Truman, Harry S. and Joe McCarthy, 1947-1967; 32082 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Failure Socialism in the U.S., 1951-1969; 32081 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Old/New Left (Education), Undated; 32080 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Truman, Harry S. and McCarthyism, Undated; 32079 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Progressive Radical Forces, 1948-1952; 32078 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Laidler, Harry and the New Deal, Undated; 32077 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Southern Tenant Farmers (New Deal and N. Thomas), 1968; 32076 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - FDR and Politics of Protest: Progressivism, 1975; 32075 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Spanish Civil War, 1936-1939; 32074 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Holocaust, 1986; 32073 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - New Deal (Background and Europe), Undated; 32072 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Blacks and Communism, 1978-1979; 32071 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Popular Front Era: Revisionists, 1985; 32070 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Kristol-Zinn Articles, 1981-1982; 32069 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Socialist Party U.S.A., 1968; 32068 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Nearing, Scott, 1976; 32067 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Communist Party U.S.A., 1973-1979; 32066 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Populism, Undated; 32065 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Populism, Undated; 32064 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - WWI: Civil Liberties, 1960-1973; 32063 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Socialist Party U.S.A., Undated; 32062 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - New Deal: Socialist Party, Undated; 32061 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Old/New Left, 1972-1982; 32060 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - New Left, Undated; 32059 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Socialism and Populism, Undated; 32058 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Debs, Eugene V., Undated; 32057 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Socialist Party, 1995; 32056 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Old/New Deal Views, 1995; 32055 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Roosevelt Presidency, Response to, Undated; 32054 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - WWII and McCarthyism, Undated; 32053 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - The Divided Left, Undated; 32052 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Hillquit, Morris, Undated; 32051 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Socialism and the "Negro", 1970; 32050 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Socialist Party, Undated; 32049 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Marxist Tradition in U.S.A., Undated; 32048 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - World Veterans Federation (on Kosovo), 1999; 32047 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Great Neck Vote, 1999; 32046 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Elections (Nassau County), 1980; 32045 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Peabody, Endicott, 1997; 32044 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Petra, Jordan, Trip to, Nov 1998; 32043 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Blank, Blanche "Degrees: Who Need Them?", 1972; 32042 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Oct 2007-Dec 2001; 32041 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - To Do/To Read, 2001; 32040 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1990s; 32039 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Holland, Letter from, 1999; 32038 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Holland Memoir, 1966; 32037 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Moslem Review, 1979; 32036 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - NYC-ADA, 1987; 32035 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - NY State Coordinating Council, 1986-1987; 32034 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - NYS-ADA, 1986-1987; 32033 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - NY ADA: Removal of Roskoff, 1985; 32032 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - NY ADA: Election Results, etc., 1982; 32031 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Goodman, Myra and Lee Dana, 1991; 32030 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Universal Utilities, 1981-1984; 32029 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Hankin, Joe, 1985-1988; 32028 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Jewish Students and the Left, 1971; 32027 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1994-Sep 1994; 32026 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Cultural Radicals, 1934, 1982; 32025 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - McCarthy, Thaddeus, 1980-1982; 32024 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Kreinder Family, 1984-1988; 32023 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Lamarche, Gary and Ellen Chuse, 1978-1987; 32022 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Union Power and New York: Victor Gotbaum and District Council 37: Reviews, 1985-1986; 32021 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995; 32020 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - ADA: Nominating Committee, 1996; 32019 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - NGO: Memo of Understanding, 1998; 32018 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - AFC-ACLU, 1983-1984; 32017 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Book Reviews, 1961-1977; 32016 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Behrens, Rose, 1978; 32015 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Feingold, Stan, 1978-1979; 32014 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Blaesser, Bill and Helen, 1978-1979; 32013 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, Jun 2000-Sep 2000; 32012 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Fund for New Priorities in America, 1999; 32011 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, Feb 2000-May 2000; 32010 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Gordon, Murray, 1985-1987; 32009 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Gorbachev letter, Reaction to, 1986; 32008 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Auschwitz: Anti-Semitism in Europe and U.S., 1970s; 32007 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Blacks and Jews, 1973-1975; 32006 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, Jun 2007-Oct 2001; 32005 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - JFK and LBJ: Social Commentary, Undated; 32004 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Black Leadership and Changes, 1970s; 32003 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - ADA: National Board, 1995-1996; 32002 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Goodlich, Michael, 1984-1993; 32001 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, 1980; 32000 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - District Council 37: Clippings, 1996-1998; 31999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - DC 37, Undated; 31998 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - ADA, Long Island Resolution, 1998; 31997 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Goodman, Barrie and Lee D., 1996; 31996 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Goodman, Lee (Memorial), 1996; 31995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - ADA Correspondence, 1997; 31994 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - ADA, Long Island Executive Committee, Sep 1998; 31993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - ADA, Long Island Executive Committee, May 1998; 31992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - ADA, 1997; 31991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Berger, Henry and Irene Jillson, 1997; 31990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - ADA Constitution, 1998; 31989 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - City College of New York Syllabi (History Class), Undated; 31988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Socialism: Amalgamated Housing, 2000; 31987 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Gus Tyler Birthday, 2001; 31986 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Uhler, Kathie, Undated; 31985 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - ADA, Long Island New Release on Milosevic, 1999; 31984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Union for Democracy Action, 1947-1954; 31983 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Partner in Education Certificate, 1979; 31982 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - CCNY Commencement Exercise Program, 1941; 31981 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - American Radicalism, 1997-1998; 31980 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Bellush Family, 1993-1999; 31979 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Bellush, Debbi, 1999; 31978 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Mom Bellush, 1943; 31977 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Bellush, Debbi, 1990-1994; 31976 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Bellush, Debbi, 1997-1998; 31975 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Bellush, Jewel, 1991; 31974 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - 80th Birthday / 50th Anniversary, 1997; 31973 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Bellush, Debbi, 2000; 31972 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - CCNY, Retirement from, 1978; 31971 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Pension forms, 1978; 31970 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Bellush, Jewel: Pension, 1983; 31969 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Bellush, Jewel: Retirement, 1974-1980; 31968 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, 1982; 31967 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Pension File, 1970-1977; 31966 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: Retirement/Pension, 1977-1978; 31965 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Bellush-Goldberg Families, 2001; 31964 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Bellush, Irv, 1985-1987; 31963 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Misc. Periodicals/Serials, 1987; 31962 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - ADA, Long Island, 2002; 31961 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.: Reviews as Governor, 1955; 31960 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Radicalism: Definition and Description, 1995; 31959 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - New Left, 1995; 31958 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Danish Socialism and the Kansas Prairie, Undated; 31957 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Socialist Administration 1927-1931, 1972; 31956 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - New Left, 1968-1971; 31955 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - The South in the Saddle: Racial Politics During the Wilson Years, Undated; 31954 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - The Communist Party of the 1930s and the New Left, Undated; 31953 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Revisionists, 1963; 31952 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - IWWW: "One Big Union", 1972-1973; 31951 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - WWI Antimilitarism and Antiradicalism, 1971-1976; 31950 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - New York State Politics Program 1893-1910, Undated; 31949 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, Undated; 31948 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - New Deal and the Blacks (Articles), 1969; 31947 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Communists and Miners: 1928-1933, 1972; 31946 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, 1980s; 31945 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Manuscript: "David Dubinsky and the Labor Wars", 2002; 31944 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Video: Interview with Bernard Bellush, Nov 1999; 31943 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Yearbook: Harford Junior College, 1969; 31942 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Women in the Abolition Movement 1830-1869 by Bellush, Jewel, 1948; 31941 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Herbert H. Lehman as Governor: Case Studies in Legislative Leadership by Bellush, Jewel, Undated; 31940 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Antioch Bookplates, Undated; 31939 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Yearbook: CUNY, 1963; 31938 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Civil Rights Audit of the National Guard, 1961; 31937 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Center for U.N. reform Education: Board of Trustees Meeting, 2001; 31936 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Family Clippings, Undated; 31935 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - ADA: Income and Inequality, 2000; 31934 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Agriculture, Corruption of, 2001; 31933 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - John Monroe High School (Misc.), 1936; 31932 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Passports (6), Undated; 31931 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Yearbook: James Monroe High School, 1936; 31930 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Yearbook: Lexicon, 1962; 31929 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Giftbook: Bellush 75th Birthday, 1993; 31928 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Tape: ADA Roosevelt Day Dinner, 1993; 31927 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Tape: Naum Ross Interview, 2001; 31926 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Tape: Handler, 1990; 31925 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Yearbook: CCNY, 1941; 31924 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - AVC: Affairs Commission, 1997; 31923 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Beder, Bernie, 1997; 31922 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Croatia: Gubic, Marijan, 1998; 31921 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - DC 37: Review of "Union Power" by Herman Benson, 1999; 31920 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - DC 37 Talk, 1999; 31919 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - American Radicalism, Undated; 31918 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - DC 37 Clippings, 1999; 31917 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Municipal Unions in Crisis, 1999; 31916 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Erabrink, Gerard and Nelly, 1997; 31915 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - A Union Saves the City, 1980; 31914 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Poland-Midrasz, 1999; 31913 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Dr. McKinley, 1993; 31912 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Wallenberg Case, 1995; 31911 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - CCNY: Faculty Senate 25th Anniversary, 1964; 31910 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Christian Identity Movement, 1999; 31909 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Christensen, Lilly K., 1988; 31908 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Dubinsky and the Communist Party, 1987; 31907 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Lower East Side Tenement Museum, 1998; 31906 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - East Europe Trip, 1990; 31905 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Farrakhan, Louis quotes, 1990; 31904 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Feingold, Stan, 1996-1997; 31903 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Ostroff, Frieda, 1997; 31902 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Freedman, Monroe, 1996; 31901 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Students, Letters from, 1978; 31900 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Israel, Fred, 1984-1986; 31899 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Hankin, Joe, 1996; 31898 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Hoffman, Manuela, Undated; 31897 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Holocaust/FDR Library, 1993; 31896 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - IRS, 1998; 31895 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Israel Articles, 1987; 31894 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Histadrut: General Federation of Labour in Israel, 1989; 31893 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Kessler, Eve (Forward), 1977; 31892 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Kibbutz, Yiftah, 1997-1998; 31891 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Labor: USA, 1991; 31890 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Land Mines and Disarmament, 1995-1996; 31889 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Levy, Uriah Phillips, 1978; 31888 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - New Deal: Civilian Conservation Corps., 1992; 31887 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Michel-Shaehar, 1996; 31886 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Pacemaker Implant, 1992; 31885 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Peabody, Endicott "Chub", 1996; 31884 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Regulski, Jerzy, 1993; 31883 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Reuther, Elisabeth, 1992; 31882 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Reuther, Walter and May, Undated; 31881 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Stoler, Mark: Israel, 1984-1994; 31880 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Tax Info for Sep. Debate, 1998; 31879 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Tellegen, Egbert: Telegrams, 1979, 1990; 31878 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Tyler, Gus: Retirement Speech, 1991; 31877 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Unemployment, Undated; 31876 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Vita, Undated; 31875 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Weinstein, Jack and Evelyn, 1978-1980; 31874 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Welfare Reform, 1997; 31873 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - World Veterans Federation, 1990-1997; 31872 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - ADA: Humphrey-Roosevelt Day Dinner Remarks, Undated; 31871 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Israeli Article, Responses to, 1988; 31870 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - ADA National Board Meeting, 2000; 31869 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - ADA Long Island: on Terrorism, 1999; 31868 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - ADA Long Island Executive Committee Meeting, 2001; 31867 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - ADA and Steve Israel, 2001; 31866 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - ADA Long Island, 2000-2001; 31865 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Affirmative Action: Colleges, 1998; 31864 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - American Jewish Committee, 2001; 31863 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Arbel, Odie, 1998-1999; 31862 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Ashkenazy, Tal, 1999; 31861 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - American Veterans Committee, 1994; 31860 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - AVC, 2001; 31859 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Arital, Collette (Israel), 1999; 31858 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - ABC Tours: Sicily, 2000; 31857 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Kosovo: ADA Resolution, 1999; 31856 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Academic Freedom: ACLU (American Civil Liberties Union), 1966; 31855 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - ADA Long island, 2000; 31854 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - ADA: Chapter Effectiveness Committee, 2000; 31853 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - ADA: Convention Planning Committee, 2000; 31852 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - ADA Long Island: Names and Addresses, 1999; 31851 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - National Board Meeting Corrections, 1999; 31850 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - ADA: NEC, 1999; 31849 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - ADA: Letter to Jontz, Jim, Bill Markus, and Amy Isaacs, 1999; 31848 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - ADA Long Island Mailing, 1999; 31847 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Bedouins and other Organizations, 1994-1999; 31846 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Ben Uri Museum: London, 2001; 31845 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Beretz, Hal, 2001; 31844 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Bisogono, Tony, 2001; 31843 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Brandeis: President Reinharz, 1998; 31842 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Brasz, Henk, 2001; 31841 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Brasz, Ineke, 1981; 31840 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Bronx Community College: Testimony re: Student Take-Over, Undated; 31839 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Carpeting, 1996; 31838 (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Carroll, Paul and Rachel, 2001; 31837 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - CCNY: History Department, 1990; 31836 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - CCNY: 60th Reunion (1941), 2001; 31835 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - CCNY: Invitation List, 2001; 31834 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Clinton Administration, 1993-1996; 31833 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - Dr. Cohen, David: NYU Medical, 2000; 31832 (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - Center for U.N. Reform Education (CURE), 2001; 31831 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - Dr. Cooper: Letter re: Surgery, 2000; 31830 (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - DC 37, 1999; 31829 (Box 18, Folder 95)
  - Debs, Eugene V., 1999; 31828 (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - Dubrovnik, Undated; 31827 (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - Elder Hostel: London, 2001; 31826 (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - FDR, the Jews and the Holocaust, 1997; 31825 (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - FDR, 1997; 31824 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Feingold, Stanley, 2000; 31823 (Box 18, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1980; 31822 (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - Tyler Articles, 1981; 31821 (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - Prospects for Peace, 2001; 31820 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - Jews and FDR, 1983-1984; 31819 (Box 18, Folder 105)
  - CCNY: Instructors Handbook, 1951; 31818 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - DPI/NGO Conference, 2001; 31817 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - It Takes Two to Tango: Dr. Blanche Blank, 1998; 31816 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - International Conference: Social Democracy, 1997; 31815 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - FDR and Jews: Articles, Undated; 31814 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Forward Articles, 1994-1997; 31813 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Small Arms Disarmament Daily, 2001; 31812 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Politics (Vermont): Sanders, Bernie, 1994; 31811 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Sanders, Bernie (Vermont), 1999; 31810 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Jews in New England, 1995; 31809 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Woodstock and Hanover Jewish Communities, 1992-1997; 31808 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Woodstock and Hanover Jewish Communities, 1993-1995; 31807 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Jews in the Upper Valley, 1991; 31806 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Sanders, Bernie, 1990; 31805 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Sanders, Bernie, 1990-1992; 31804 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Veterans Unit: Articles, 2000; 31803 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Sample Essays, 2001; 31802 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Veterans: Background Documents, Undated; 31801 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - College Newspapers, 1940s; 31800 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Commission on State-City Relations, 1971; 31799 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Commission on State-City Relations, 1972; 31798 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - 616th Ordnance Ammunition Company: WWII, Undated; 31797 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - The Living History Project Final Report, 1978; 31796 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Senate: Retirement Remarks, 1977; 31795 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - City University Committee on Enrollment Policies, 1964; 31794 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 1984 Election Results, Analysis, 1988; 31793 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1993; 31792 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1993-Sep 1993; 31791 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1995-Sep 1995; 31790 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1993-Oct 1993; 31789 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1993-Apr 1993; 31788 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Israel, 1983; 31787 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Roosevelt, N.J., 1992-1993; 31786 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Jan 2007-Mar 2001; 31785 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1979-Jun 1979; 31784 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1980-May 1980; 31783 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Feb 1982; 31782 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Brown, Theresa, 1980-1981; 31781 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1975-Dec 1975; 31780 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Judicial Conference: Victor Gotbaum, 1965; 31779 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Victor Gotbaum vs. Wurf, 1978-1979; 31778 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Victor Gotbaum: Correspondence, 1978; 31777 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Victor Gotbaum: Correspondence, 1975-1979; 31776 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Victor Gotbaum: Speeches, Articles, 1976-1977; 31775 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Victor Gotbaum: White House Fellows and Misc., 1970s-1980s; 31774 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Undated; 31773 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Corruption in DC 37?, 1970; 31772 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Victor Gotbaum and OCB, 1978; 31771 (Box 20, Folder 26)